{
    "id": "57dedef1b1ca4cc586c3c9e73fcdc561",
    "title": "Verb Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. the Minister tomorrow.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about future events if the arrangement already exists. ",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing",
                "will see"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you …………………. this weekend?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "doing",
                "done"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… thirty-seven next month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will turn",
                "would turn",
                "turned"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Buses ……………….. every five minutes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "will leave",
                "are leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This time tomorrow I ..................... my exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will write",
                "will be writing",
                "am writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I knew she ………………… arrive before long.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will phone you when I ………………… time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "will have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will follow you wherever you ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "are going",
                "have gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What ……………….. we ……………….. for dinner?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do, have",
                "are, having",
                "will, be having"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… the money on the 20th.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am needing",
                "will need",
                "would need"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}